Monster Island is a animation, adventure, family
film directed by Leopoldo Aguilar.
Young Lucas finds out he's not really a human after he surprisingly transforms
into a monster in front of the most popular kids at school.
His search for Monster Island and his real roots takes him on a fabulously scary journey that puts him face to
face with more tentacles, fangs and far-out situations than he can shake one of his new wings at.
Lucas (voice), played by Phillip Adrian Vasquez.
Dina / Old Lady / Teacher (voice), played by Nancy Sullivan.
Carlotta / Patrick's Mom (voice), played by Katie Leigh.
Veronica (voice), played by Fiona Hardingham.
Kuro / Lagoon Monster (voice), played by Wally Wingert.
Melanie / Cameron's Mom / Child Patrick / Monster #4 /
Monster #13 (voice), played by Jenifer Kaplan.
Monster Island (released as Isla Calaca in Mexico) is a 2017 English-language
Mexican animated horror comedy film directed by Leopoldo Aguilar.
The film was produced by Ánima Estudios and animated
by India's Discreet Arts Production.
The film was first released in the United Kingdom on 21 July
2017, and later in Mexico on 14 September 2017.
The film was released in the United States on 1
September 2017 on home media and VOD platforms.
The film explores themes of monster, transformation, school.
The tone is lighthearted.